<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Year of St. Joseph</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter passcode</string>
    <string name="reminder_hint">Reminder</string>
    <string name="button_send">Submit</string>

    <string-array name="devotions">
        <item>Prayer</item>
        <item>Indulgences</item>
        <item>Litany</item>
        <item>Novena</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>Prayer for Saint Joseph\'s intercession before God</item>
        <item>Indulgences for the year of Saint Joseph</item>
        <item>Litany to St. Joseph</item>
        <item>9 Day Novena to St. Joseph</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="content">
        <item>
            To you, O blessed Joseph,
            \ndo we come in our tribulation,
            \nand having implored the help of your most holy Spouse,
            \nwe confidently invoke your patronage also.
            \nThrough that charity which bound you
            \nto the Immaculate Virgin Mother of God
            \nand through the paternal love
            \nwith which you embraced the Child Jesus,
            \nwe humbly beg you graciously to regard the inheritance
            \nwhich Jesus Christ has purchased by his Blood,
            \nand with your power and strength to aid us in our necessities.

            \n\nO most watchful guardian of the Holy Family,
            \ndefend the chosen children of Jesus Christ;
            \nO most loving father, ward off from us
            \nevery contagion of error and corrupting influence;
            \nO our most mighty protector, be kind to us
            \nand from heaven assist us in our struggle
            \nwith the power of darkness.
            \nAs once you rescued the Child Jesus from deadly peril,
            \nso now protect God\'s Holy Church
            \nfrom the snares of the enemy and from all adversity;
            \nshield, too, each one of us by your constant protection,
            \nso that, supported by your example and your aid,
            \nwe may be able to live piously, to die in holiness,
            \nand to obtain eternal happiness in heaven.
            \nAmen.
        </item>


        <item>
            A plenary indulgence is granted under the usual conditions (sacramental confession,
            Eucharistic Communion, and prayer for the intentions of the Holy Father)
            to the faithful who, with a spirit detached from any sin, participate in the Year of
            Saint Joseph on the following occasions and manners:

            \n\n•	Meditate for at least 30 minutes on the Lord\'s Prayer
            \n\n•	Participate in a spiritual retreat of at least one day that includes a meditation on Saint Joseph
            \n\n•	Following the example of Saint Joseph, perform a corporal or spiritual work of mercy
            \n\n•	Pray the Rosary together with one’s family (or as an engaged couple) in order that
                “all Christian families may be stimulated to recreate the same atmosphere of
                intimate communion, love and prayer that was in the Holy Family.”
            \n\n•	Entrust one’s work daily to the protection of Saint Joseph
            \n\n•	Pray for St. Joseph’s intercession for the unemployed that they might find dignifying work

            \n\n•	Recite any of the following for persecuted Christians:
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Litany of St. Joseph
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Akathistos to St. Joseph
                \n\t\t\t\t (in the Byzantine tradition)
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Another liturgical prayer to St. Joseph
            \n\n•	Pray an approved prayer or perform an act of piety in honor of St. Joseph on the following occasions:
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Sunday after Christmas
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Feast of St. Joseph on March 19
                \n\t\t\t⁃ 19th of any month
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Wednesdays
                \n\t\t\t\t (the day traditionally dedicated to St. Joseph)
                \n\t\t\t⁃ Feast of St. Joseph the Worker on May 1
        </item>


        <item>
            \ Lord, have mercy on us.\n
            Christ, have mercy on us.\n
            Lord, have mercy on us.\n
            Jesus, hear us,	Jesus, graciously hear us.\n
            \n
            God the Father of heaven, have mercy on us.\n
            God the Son, Redeemer of the World.\n
            God the Holy Spirit.\n
            Holy Trinity, one God.\n
            \n
            Holy Mary,  pray for us.\n
            St. Joseph, pray for us.\n
            Renowned offspring of David,\n
            Light of Patriarchs,\n
            Spouse of the Mother of God,\n
            Chaste guardian of the Virgin,\n
            Foster father of the Son of God,\n
            Diligent protector of Christ,\n
            \n
            Head of the Holy Family, 	pray for us.\n
            Joseph most just,	\n
            Joseph most chaste,	\n
            Joseph most prudent, \n
            Joseph most strong,	\n
            Joseph most obedient,	\n
            Joseph most faithful,	\n
            Mirror of patience,	\n
            \n
            Lover of poverty, 	pray for us.\n
            Model of artisans,	\n
            Glory of home life,	\n
            Guardian of virgins,	\n
            Pillar of families,	\n
            Solace of the wretched,	\n
            Hope of the sick,	\n
            Patron of the dying,	\n
            Terror of demons,	\n
            Protector of Holy Church,	\n
            \n
            Lamb of God, \n who takes away the sins of the world,\n	spare us, O Jesus.\n
            \n
            Lamb of God, \n who takes away the sins of the world,\n	graciously hear us, O Jesus.\n
            \n
            Lamb of God, \n who takes away the sins of the world,\n have mercy on us, O Jesus.\n
            \n
            He made him the lord of his household \n And prince over all his possessions.\n
            \n
            Let us pray:\n
            \nO God, in your ineffable providence you were pleased to choose Blessed Joseph
            to be the spouse of your most holy Mother; grant, we beg you,
            that we may be worthy to have him for our intercessor in heaven whom on earth
            we venerate as our Protector. You who live and reign forever and ever.\n
            \n
            Saint Joseph, pray for us!</item>

        <item>Soon to arrive</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>